Dillon J. Ellis

Creative Solutions to Complex Problems

CONTACT

(770)-561-0377 www.dillonzellis.com dillonzellis@gmail.com Atlanta, GA

SKILLS

Expertise in various computer languages, frameworks, and databases focusing web design.

Custom Wordpress, JavaScript, SQL, PHP, SASS, HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, Node, MongoDB, Express, REST API, and EJS.

Proficiency in Figma, Git, Github, NPM, Gulp, VSCode. Microsoft Office Word, PowerPoint, & Excel.

ADDITIONAL SKILLS

Analytical Thinking
Problem Solving
Team Leadership
Organization
Problem Solving
Management Skills & Flexible
Strong Communication

REFERENCES

References available upon request.

CAREER OBJECTIVE

Hard-working, motivated individual. Well versed in various computer languages focusing web development with a background in empirical research studies from design to analyzing data. Possesses a Bachelor of Science, impeccable written and verbal communication skills, and excellent interpersonal skills.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

DZ Designs - Atlanta, GA

Owner, Design, and Development - Jan 2019 - Present

- · Acquired Clients.
- Conducted client meetings to determine client needs for development and budget.
- Design and Develop product.
- Set up maintenance packages including hosting, updates, revisions, backups, and security.

RLM Affairs - Gainesville, GA

Assistant Event Organizer - March 2017 - Present

- Tailored events according to the personal tastes and budgets of clients, managing and exceeding expectations.
- Maintained a portfolio of vendors and clients.
 Serving as primary point of contact.

RLM Florist - Gainesville, GA

Assistant Manager and IT - January 2017 - Present

- Create, update, and maintain store ecommerce site with seasonal products and custom shipping and payment gateways.
- Address and resolve guest concerns, maintaining brand loyalty and increasing customer satisfaction ratings
- · Train staff to deliver outstanding customer service.

EDUCATION

University of North Georgia - Dalonegha, GA

Bachelor of Science in Psychological Sciences, GPA 3.6/4.0 - Dec 2017

University of North Georgia - Gainesville, GA

Associate of Arts in Psychological Sciences, GPA 3.7/4.0 - May 2015

Relevant Coursework: Statistics, Research Methods, Web Programming, Software Engineering, and Databases.

Awards and Honors: Independent research in review of publication and SEPA reginonal Conference presentations.